Local 1199 Photograph Files 5933 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- New York Blood Center Job Action (July 17, 1980): pics of members walking off the job (Box 68, Folder 62)
  #2851
- Lincoln Hospital Grievances: two blood-gas technicians get 3, 000 checks from BP Steve Frankel, 7/1980 (Box 68, Folder 63)
  #2852
- Valhaller Blood Drive, 8/1980 (Box 68, Folder 64)
  #2853
- Drug Negotiators, 8/1980 (Box 68, Folder 65)
  #2854
- Joggers fail mugger (Box 68, Folder 66)
  #2855
- King Center Delegates, 8/1980 (Box 68, Folder 67)
  #2856
- Bill Rodgers with 1199ers: University Hospital workers, Aug. 1, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 68)
  #2857
- New England T-Shirts, 8/1980 (Box 68, Folder 69)
  #2858
- CSS: Community Service Society of N.Y. - Informational Pickets (Box 68, Folder 70)
  #2859
- Retirees Art Show, 6/1980 (Box 68, Folder 71)
  #2859a
- Hispanic Retirees Dance/Banquet, 7/1980 (Box 68, Folder 72)
  #2859b
- Spanish Affairs Committee meets Delegates from El Salvador (Box 68, Folder 73)
  #2860
- Barbara Pearlsten, 8/1980 (Box 68, Folder 74)
  #2861
- 1199 C Training Fund Dinner, 8/15/1980 (Box 68, Folder 75)
  #2862
- King Center Grievance - Juan Martinez, 8/1980 (Box 68, Folder 76)
  #2863
- New York Medical College / M.R.I. (vote Strike Mangt. Sept. 2) (Box 68, Folder 77)
  #2864
- Nursing Home Care Conference, 9/1980 (Box 68, Folder 78)
  #2865
- Catholic Tenders Demo, 9/1980 (Box 68, Folder 79)
  #2866
- St. Barnabas PAs, 9/1980 (Box 68, Folder 80)
  #2867
- RN Delegates, Sept. 1980 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  #2868
- RN Delegates weekend, Sept. 1980 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- RN delegates weekend, 9/1980 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- RN delegates Weekend, Sept. 1980 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Training Fund - Doctor + Dentist Students, 9/1980 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  #2869
- St. Raphael's Hospital Election, 9/1980 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  #2870
- Lydia Rodriguez, 1199 Technician poisoned by Xylene, 7/1980 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  #2871 -- Negs transferred to #2845, same subject and shoot --- EMPTY
- Rosemary Chung: 1199 College Tuition Aid (Box 69, Folder 8)
  #2872
- Bill Rodgers with 1199ers (Box 69, Folder 9)
  #2873
- Mary Daley + Pat DiCristofold Training Grads, 9/1980 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  #2874
- Judy Sheudan - Training Fund RN Grad, 10/1980 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  #2875
- Geiger, Elizabeth, 11/1980 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  #2876
- Daughters of Jacob Pre-Strike Meetings, 11/1980 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  #2877
- Michigan Nurses HMCRNO, 11/1980 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  #2878
- N.J. Women's Conference, Nov. 13, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  #2879
- Home Care Workers, 11/1980 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  #2880
- 1199 J Oct. Del. Assembly, United Hospital Delegates, Peter Rodino, Organizee Pollace, 11/1980 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  #2881
- Jeanne Stellman at 1199, Nov. 1980 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  #2882
- Lewin Corey at 1199, 11/14/1980 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  #2883
- Debby King at Comparable Worth Conference, 11/1980 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  #2884
- Gloria Williams, Oct. 1980 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  #2885
- Velma, Chlo, Doreen, Victor Weinburg, 11/1980 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  #2886
- St. Barnabas NJ RNs, July 1980 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  #2887
- Baltimore Negotiations, 11/1980 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  #2888
- St. Clare + Hospital (Box 69, Folder 25)
  #2889
- Manhattan Eye + Ear Victory (Box 69, Folder 26)
  #2890
- Maternity Infant Care (Box 69, Folder 27)
  #2891
- New York Blood Center Hepatitis B Vaccine Program (Box 69, Folder 28)
  #2892
- AECOM Demonstration (Box 69, Folder 29)
  #2893
- Long Island Hospital Ratification Vote (Box 69, Folder 30)
  #2894
- Mount Sinai - Sick Policy Demonstration (Box 69, Folder 31)
  #2895
- Resthaven Nursing Home (Box 69, Folder 32)
  #2896
- St. Raphael's Hospital (Box 69, Folder 33)
  #2897
- Massachusetts Health Care Professionals Union (Box 69, Folder 34)
  #2898
- Luce Rocque (Box 69, Folder 35)
  #2899
- J.P. Stevens Demonstration (Box 69, Folder 36)
  #2900
- Elizabeth Holtzman (Box 69, Folder 37)
  #2901
- Baltimore Strike See Major Events, 12/1980 (Box 69, Folder 38)
  #2902 -- EMPTY
- 19 Connecticut Nursing Homes Strike: Nov. 1980, Also Ruth Tenica, RN (Box 69, Folder 39)
  #2903
- Lorraine Manor Nursing Home Rally, Dec. 7, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 40)
  #2904
- Amityville RNs, 12/1980 (Box 69, Folder 41)
  #2905
- Retiree Conference, 12/1980 (Box 69, Folder 42)
  #2907
- 1199 J Presents Check for Italian Quake Victims, 1/1981 (Box 69, Folder 43)
  #2908
- Al Evanoff, Lorraine Seidel, Aberdeen, Organizers, Jan. 28, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 44)
  #2910
- St. Barnabas RNs (NJ) Strike, Feb. 1981 (Box 69, Folder 45)
  #2911
- Victor Garcia 1199 J V.P., 2/1981 (Box 69, Folder 46)
  #2912
- Burnt Out RN, 2/1981 (Box 69, Folder 47)
  #2913
- Bailey RN organizer, Feb. 1981 (Box 69, Folder 48)
  #2914
- St. Clare Techs. + RN Election Win, Feb. 1981 (Box 69, Folder 49)
  #2915
- Physician's Assistants (Box 69, Folder 50)
  #2916
- Aprian Cruz, 1199 Member at University Hospital (fired for Union activity) (Box 69, Folder 51)
  #2917
- Pautakon, Kathleen - Univ. Hospital Worker - Arbitration Victory (Box 69, Folder 52)
  #2918
- Angell Memorial Animal Hospital, Boston, MA, Liz Manlial, Bennie Jones, 1199 Delegates (Box 69, Folder 53)
  #2919
- Muehlenhamp Mug Shot, 2/1981 (Box 69, Folder 54)
  #2920
- Nigerian Visitor Mallam Halibu, Feb. 1981 (Box 69, Folder 55)
  #2921
- Nigerian Unionist, March 1981 (Box 69, Folder 56)
  #2922
- Barbaro heaving, 2/26/1981 (Box 69, Folder 57)
  #2923
- Roca Parks, Burt Silverman drawing (Box 69, Folder 58)
  #2924
- Images of Labor (negative) (Box 69, Folder 59)
  #2925
- OSHA Class (Graduation + Staff Class Speakers), 12/1980 (Box 69, Folder 60)
  #2926
- Negative of Paul Doms painting for Images of Labor Book - Bread + Roses Project, 3/31/1981 (Box 69, Folder 61)
  #2927
- 1199 M Founding Convention, March 1981 (Box 69, Folder 62)
  #2928
- 1199 M Founding Convention, mar. 1981 (Box 69, Folder 63)
- NJ Dance, 3/1981 (Box 69, Folder 64)
  #2929
- Arlene Eratly in 1199 M, 3/1981 (Box 69, Folder 65)
  #2930
- 1199 Publications: 1199A Family Portrait, Mine and Mill; Earl Dotter Lawrence, 1912 the Bread + Roses Strike -- The Working American Records: Take Care Ossie + Ruby, march 25, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 66)
  #2931
- Labor + the Arts and Humanities Conference, Dec. 6, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 67)
  #2932
- Alan Havesil/Judy Buehl, Joanna Miller (Box 69, Folder 68)
  #2933
- Connecticut Member visit Mental Health Group Time (Box 69, Folder 69)
  #2934
- Haym Salomon Injuries (Box 69, Folder 70)
  #2935
- Liz Geiger (Box 69, Folder 71)
  #2936
- King Washington Demonstration (Box 70, Folder 1)
  #2937
- LICH Tech. Victory (Box 70, Folder 2)
  #2938
- Norberto Sabater Boxer - 1199er's son (Box 70, Folder 3)
  #2939
- Irwin Corey the Writer (Box 70, Folder 4)
  #2940
- Barbara Ingram (Box 70, Folder 5)
  #2941
- Health + Safety Committee meeting, Apr. 1, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  #2942
- Patti Deitch, 1199C Sec. Wkr. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  #2944
- Myths of Aging - Retiree Class, 4/1981 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  #2945
- Joanna Miller, 4/1981 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  #2946
- Bronx-Lebanon Hosp. - 'No Pay-No Work' - April 9th - no Medicaid money - no pay demonstrations at Fulton Ave. division (Box 70, Folder 10)
  #2947
- Bronx-Lebanon Demonstration - Strike, Apr. 9 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  #2948
- April 16 - 1199 - Medicaid demonstration (NY Public Library) (Box 70, Folder 12)
  #2949
- Justo Rivera Einstein, Dark-room Tech. Retired (Box 70, Folder 13)
  #2950
- Ameico Duran - Member Democratic Revolutionary Front: Speaks at 1199, April 15 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  #2951
- JIGC - Staff Talent Show (Box 70, Folder 15)
  #2952
- Wisconsin Safety Conference, Apr. 1981 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  #2953
- Washington - El Salvador Rally, May 1981 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  #2954
- Gary Ind. Party, 5/1981 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  #2955
- Highlands Regional Strike, 5/1981 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  #2956
- May 3, Washington Rally - El Salvador, May 1981 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  #2957
- Wisconsin OSHA Conference, May, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  #2958
- Ezrath/Michigan Michigan Delegates, May 1981 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  #2959
- Nurses Network Conference, May 1981 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  #2960
- Retirees - at demo 2/portraits, May 1981 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  #2961
- Roosevelt members sign budget cut postcards, May 1981 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  #2962
- Lenox Hill RNs count ratification ballots, May 1981 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  #2963
- SEIU photo negs, 5/1981 (Box 70, Folder 27)
  #2964
- Michigan installation, 5/1981 (Box 70, Folder 28)
  #2965
- Mabel Pamphile, 6/1981 (Box 70, Folder 29)
  #2966
- SEIU Women's conference, 6/1981 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  #2967
- Highland Regional Medical Center - Kluckol's Security violent guards vs. women health care workers, June, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 31)
  #2968
- St. Clare's Clerical Workers, May, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 32)
  #2969
- 10th Annual Health Care Conference - June, 1981, 'Health Care for the Senior Citizen', June, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 33)
  #2970
- Barbara Ingram's 'going away' party, May, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 34)
  #2971
- Oral History Workshop with Lewis Cole, June 1981 (Box 70, Folder 35)
  #2972
- Hispanic Affairs Committee Honors Leon J. Davis, June 27, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 36)
  #2973
- St. John's Episcopal Hospital Progressive Action Club, June, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 37)
  #2974
- Barbara for mayor Press Conference, June 1981 (Box 70, Folder 38)
  #2975
- Karin Batten - exhibitor 1199 gallery, Sept. 1981: shots at Artist's Studio, June 1981 (Box 70, Folder 39)
  #2976
- Irwin 'the Union Buster' (Box 70, Folder 40)
  #2977
- JIGC - Talent Show (Box 70, Folder 41)
  #2978
- Amy Neller (Box 70, Folder 42)
  #2979
- March through the South Bronx: protest budget cuts, June 27 (Box 70, Folder 43)
  #2980
- Camp Vacamas, 7/1981 (Box 70, Folder 44)
  #2981
- Retiree Art Show, July 1981 (Box 70, Folder 45)
  #2982
- First Aid Course, 7/1981 (Box 70, Folder 46)
  #2983
- Woodhull Contract Signed, 7/1981 (Box 70, Folder 47)
  #2984
- Jerry Brown, 7/1981 (Box 70, Folder 48)
  #2985
- LaGuardia HIP Strike, 7/16/1981 (Box 70, Folder 49)
  #2986
- May budget Rally - NY, 5/1981 (Box 70, Folder 50)
  #2987
- N.J. Strike - Hot Day!, 7/1981 (Box 70, Folder 51)
  #2988
- LICH RNs, 7/1981 (Box 70, Folder 52)
  #2989
- First Aid Class, 7/1981 (Box 70, Folder 53)
  #2990
- Michigan LPNs, 7/1981 (Box 70, Folder 54)
  #2991
- Highlands Regional Medical Center, June 1981 (Box 70, Folder 55)
  #2992
- Judy Ocasio - Legal Aide, Delegate enters, law school, July 1981 (Box 70, Folder 56)
  #2993
- Frank Boyland - 1199 Organizer won City Councilman, July, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 57)
  #2994
- Myrtle Hartfield sworn in ABC, 7/1981 (Box 70, Folder 58)
  #2995
- Triplets - University Settlement, 8/1981 (Box 70, Folder 59)
  #2996
- East Baltimore Med. plan, 8/1981 (Box 70, Folder 60)
  #2997
- Inge Averbacher, 7/1981 (Box 70, Folder 61)
  #2998 -- EMPTY
- Cedrion Solomon (NYU, LPN) Retires, 8/1981 (Box 70, Folder 62)
  #2999
- 1199/NE (Boston) Benefit Dance, 7/11 (Box 70, Folder 63)
- Retiree Lawyer, 8/1981 (Box 70, Folder 64)
  #3001
- Aura Escobar, 8/1981 (Box 70, Folder 65)
  #3002
- CLUW Carribbean dinner (by Nortls) (Box 70, Folder 66)
  #3003
- Carrier election win - RNs, 8/1981 (Box 70, Folder 67)
  #3004
- Debbie for Solidarity Day Cover, Aug. 1981 (Box 70, Folder 68)
  #3005
- St. Clare's ratifies contract, 9/9 (Box 70, Folder 69)
  #3006
- Women's Barbaro Brkfst, 8/1981 (Box 70, Folder 70)
- PATCO Rally, 8/1981 (Box 70, Folder 71)
  #3008
- PATCO at RN Assembly, 8/1981 (Box 70, Folder 72)
  #3009
- Dental Plan - 10-year staffers, 9/1981 (Box 70, Folder 73)
  #3010
- Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 2)
- frame 15a, 22a (Box 71, Folder 3)
- frame 5,6,9,10 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- frame 4a,5a,6a (Box 71, Folder 5)
- frame (2) 18a, 22a, 23a, 27a (Box 71, Folder 6)
- frame 7, 8, 12, 29a (Box 71, Folder 7)
- frame 31a, 18a (Box 71, Folder 8)
  #665a
- frame 18a, 25a, 21a, 30a (Box 71, Folder 9)
  #665b
- frame 13a, 21a, 30, 23, 11a, 32 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  #665c
- frame 32a, 31a (Box 71, Folder 11)
  #665d
- frame 30 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- frame 6a, 10a, 12a (Box 71, Folder 13)
- frame 3, 7, 10, 19, 20, 30a, 32a (Box 71, Folder 14)
- frame 10a, 12a (Box 71, Folder 15)
- frame 2a, 3a, 4a, 5a, 7a, 8a (Box 71, Folder 16)
- frame 11a, 12a, 13a, 15, 18 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- frame 12a, 9a, 10a, 7, 25a, 18a (Box 71, Folder 18)
- frame 11, 14, 17, 18 (Box 71, Folder 19)
- frame all (12) (Box 71, Folder 20)
  #799
- frame 5a, 11a, 18a (Box 71, Folder 21)
- frame 2a, 3a, 7a, 12a, 13a, 14, 14a, 15a, 17, 18a (Box 71, Folder 22)
- frame 2, 3, 3a, 7a, 10, 11, 12, 14, 17, 18, 20 (Box 71, Folder 23)
- frame 6, 8, 9, 10, 12, 16, 21, 22, 23, 25 (Box 71, Folder 24)
- frame 5 6, 9a, 10a, 11a, 14a, 17a, 22a, 30a, 33a (Box 71, Folder 25)
  #872a
- frame 5a, 7a, 9a, 12a, 18a, 26a, 30a (Box 71, Folder 26)
  #872b
- frame 3a, 7, 13a, 27, 31a (Box 71, Folder 27)
  #872c
- frame 12a, 13a, 23, 27 (Box 71, Folder 28)
- frame 3, 5, 10, 11, 14a, 15a (Box 71, Folder 29)
- frame 5, 7, 11, 15, 18, 19 (Box 71, Folder 30)
- frame 6a, 8a, 10a, 11a, 12a, 13a (Box 71, Folder 31)
- frame 2a, 9a (Box 71, Folder 32)
- frame 9a, 10a, 7a, 8a, 18a, 19a, 20a (Box 71, Folder 33)
- frame 3a, 5a, 7a, 6a, 8a, 14a, 17a, 20a (Box 71, Folder 34)
- frame 5a, 6a (Box 71, Folder 35)
- frame 5a, 6, 6a, 12a, 15a, 18a, 21 (Box 71, Folder 36)
- frame 4a, 5a, 6a, 9a, 10a, 12a, 15a (Box 71, Folder 37)
  #961a
- frame 1a, 3a, 7a, 8a, 11a, 13a, 18a (Box 71, Folder 38)
  #961b
- frame 6, 14 (Box 71, Folder 39)
- frame 2a, 4a, 10a, 14a, 16a (Box 71, Folder 40)
  #963a
- frame 6a, 11a, 14a, 15a, 18a (Box 71, Folder 41)
  #963b
- frame 3, 8, 9, 10, 11, 13a, 15, 15a, 16, 20a (Box 71, Folder 42)
- frame 3, 5a, 8, 11, 19a, 20a (Box 71, Folder 43)
- frame 4, 5, 12a, 13, 13a, 18a (Box 71, Folder 44)
- frame 1a, 2a, 7 (Box 71, Folder 45)
- frame 10a, 12a, 16, 17, 19a (Box 71, Folder 46)
- frame 8, 9, 18, 19, 35 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  #1028
- frame 7, 8, 11, 14, 15, 16, 17, 20, 20a (Box 71, Folder 48)
- frame 7, 8 (Box 71, Folder 49)
- frame 3a, 5a, 7a (Box 71, Folder 50)
- frame 2, 4, 6a, 7a, 11a, 13a, 23 (Box 71, Folder 51)
- frame 10, 11a, 4a, 20 (Box 71, Folder 52)
- frame 11, 12, 14,15, 21 (Box 71, Folder 53)
  #1159a
- frame 14, 16a (Box 71, Folder 54)
  #1159b
- frame 21, 24, 25 (Box 71, Folder 55)
- frame 12a, 17, 20a (Box 71, Folder 56)
- frame 9, 10, 11, 13, 17a, 18a, 19 (Box 71, Folder 57)
- frame 5a, 6a, 7a, 8, 23a, 27a (Box 71, Folder 58)
- frame 15, 15a, 17a, 20, 23a (Box 71, Folder 59)
- frame 32, 33,34,35 (Box 71, Folder 60)
- frame 16, 16a, 19 (Box 71, Folder 61)
- frame 7a, 13, 14,20a (Box 71, Folder 62)
  #1292
- frame 2 (Box 71, Folder 63)
- frame 4a, 5a, 8, 10a, 11a (Box 71, Folder 64)
- frame 5, 6, 7, 9, 17a, 18a (Box 71, Folder 65)
- frame 12, 13, 14, 18, 19, 20, 20a (Box 71, Folder 66)
- frame 2, 5, 8, 14, 18, 24, 29 (Box 71, Folder 67)
- frame 6, 9, 11 (Box 71, Folder 68)
- frame 10, 15, 19 (Box 71, Folder 69)
- frame 2, 5, 10a, 11a, 14, 19, 20 (Box 71, Folder 70)
- frame 3, 5, 6, 8, 11, 14a, 17 (Box 71, Folder 71)
  #1411a
- frame 3, 5, 12a (Box 71, Folder 72)
  #1411b
- frame 7a, 8, 10a, 11 (Box 71, Folder 73)
  #1411c
- frame 5a, 7a (Box 71, Folder 74)
- frame 2, 6, 8 (Box 71, Folder 75)
- frame 10a, 13a, 15, 18 (Box 71, Folder 76)
- frame 4, 6, 6a, 7a, 14a, 20a (Box 71, Folder 77)
- frame 3, 11, 14, 15, 20a (Box 71, Folder 78)
- frame 7, 8, 11, 14, 17 (Box 71, Folder 79)
- frame 6, 12, 17, 19 (Box 71, Folder 80)
- frame 16, 31, 35, 29 (Box 71, Folder 81)
  #93
- frame 5a, 6a, 7a, 8a, 11a, 32a, 21a (Box 71, Folder 82)
- frame 2, 5, 9, 19, 20, 21 (Box 71, Folder 83)
  #100a
- frame 18-19, 20 (Box 71, Folder 84)
  #100b
- frame 7, 8 (Box 71, Folder 85)
- frame 0, 1a, 5a, 17a (Box 71, Folder 86)
- frame 9, 15, 20 (Box 71, Folder 87)
- frame 16a, 17a, 18a, 13a, 20, 30a (Box 71, Folder 88)
- frame 17 (Box 71, Folder 89)
- frame 6, 17, 23, 24,30a, 32, 35, 36 (Box 71, Folder 90)
  #377a
- frame 11, 13, 17,18, 20, 29 (Box 71, Folder 91)
  #377b
- frame 4, 10, 16, 18,20, 22 (Box 71, Folder 92)
  #377c
- frame 6a, 7a, 19, 20, 31a (Box 71, Folder 93)
  #377d
- frame 10a, 11a, 8, 9 (Box 71, Folder 94)
  #1453a
- frame 4, 6, 10a (Box 71, Folder 95)
  #1453b
- frame 3, 6, 7, 8, 10, 19 (Box 71, Folder 96)
- frame 5a, 10, 9, 15, 15a (Box 71, Folder 97)
- frame 7a, 8a, 9a, 10a, 16a (Box 71, Folder 98)
  #1462b
- frame 5a, 8a, 18a (Box 71, Folder 99)
- frame 1, 5, 9, 13, 14 (Box 71, Folder 100)
- frame 6a, 14a, 15a, 16a (Box 71, Folder 101)
  #1471a
- frame 3, 7, 9 (Box 71, Folder 102)
  #1471b
- frame 8a, 11a, 12a, 15a, 16a (Box 71, Folder 103)
- frame 13a, 14, 16 (Box 71, Folder 104)
- frame 2a, 11, 12, 13, 17a, 18a, 22, 25a, 35a (Box 71, Folder 105)
- frame 12, 19 (Box 71, Folder 106)
- frame 4a, 7, 9, 15a, 20a (Box 71, Folder 107)
- frame 6, 8, 12a, 13a, 20 (Box 71, Folder 108)
- frame 1a, 3a, 7a, 9a, 12a, 18a (Box 71, Folder 109)
- frame 3, 6a, 7a, 9, 10, 12, 13a, 14a, 18a (Box 71, Folder 110)
- frame 2a (Box 71, Folder 111)
- frame 5a, 7, 8, 9a, 14 (Box 71, Folder 112)
- frame 3, 4, 5, 6, 7 (Box 71, Folder 113)
- frame 16a, 20a (Box 71, Folder 114)
- frame 5, 7, 8 (Box 71, Folder 115)
- frame 2a, 4, 6, 14, 17 (Box 71, Folder 116)
  #1679a
- frame 11a, 15a (Box 71, Folder 117)
  #1679b
- frame 3a, 8, 12, 15a, 16a (Box 71, Folder 118)
  #1694a
- frame 2a, 4, 5, 9a, 11a (Box 71, Folder 119)
  #1694b
- frame 3a, 4a, 5a, 7a, 14a, 16a (Box 71, Folder 120)
  #1694c
- frame 5a, 6a, 9a, 10a, 12a (Box 71, Folder 121)
- frame 8, 10, 15a, 16a, 17a (Box 71, Folder 122)
- frame 2, 4, 7, 8 (Box 71, Folder 123)
- frame 5, 9, 17a, 25, 36 (Box 71, Folder 124)
- frame 3, 9, 12, 14, 29 (Box 71, Folder 125)
  #1813a
- #1813b (Box 71, Folder 126)
- frame 6, 19, 20a (Box 71, Folder 127)
  #1813c
- frame 4a, 5a, 6, 8a, 9a, 12, 13, 13a, 14a, 15a, 17a, 18 (Box 71, Folder 128)
  #1813d
- #1813E (Box 71, Folder 129)
- #1813F (Box 71, Folder 130)
- #1828 (Box 71, Folder 131)
- #1853 (Box 71, Folder 132)
- #1863 (Box 71, Folder 133)
- #1874 (Box 71, Folder 134)
- #1876 (Box 71, Folder 135)
- #1880 (Box 71, Folder 136)
- #1898 (Box 71, Folder 137)
- #1918 (Box 71, Folder 138)
- #1922 (Box 71, Folder 139)
- #1925 (Box 71, Folder 140)
- #1926 (Box 71, Folder 141)
- #1950 (Box 71, Folder 142)
- #1954 (Box 71, Folder 143)
- #1966 (Box 71, Folder 144)
- #2018a (Box 71, Folder 145)
- #2018b (Box 71, Folder 146)
- #2033a (Box 71, Folder 147)
- #2033b (Box 71, Folder 148)
- #2047a (Box 71, Folder 149)
- #2047b (Box 71, Folder 150)
- #2084 (Box 71, Folder 151)
- #2029 (Box 71, Folder 152)
- #2093 (Box 71, Folder 153)
- #2098 (Box 71, Folder 154)
- #2138 (Box 71, Folder 155)
- #2147 (Box 71, Folder 156)
- #2152a (Box 71, Folder 157)
- #2152b (Box 71, Folder 158)
- #2152c (Box 71, Folder 159)
- #2158 (Box 71, Folder 160)
- #2161a (Box 71, Folder 161)
- #2161b (Box 71, Folder 162)
- #2161c (Box 71, Folder 163)
- #2215 (Box 71, Folder 164)
- #2254 (Box 71, Folder 165)
- #2258 (Box 71, Folder 166)
- #2260 (Box 71, Folder 167)
- #2270 (Box 71, Folder 168)
- #2273 (Box 71, Folder 169)
- #2302 (Box 71, Folder 170)
- #2328 (Box 71, Folder 171)
- #2334 (Box 71, Folder 172)
- #2344 (Box 71, Folder 173)
- #2346 (Box 71, Folder 174)
- #2423 (Box 71, Folder 175)
- #2438 (Box 71, Folder 176)
- #2467a (Box 71, Folder 177)
- #2467b (Box 71, Folder 178)
- #2467c (Box 71, Folder 179)
- #2493a (Box 71, Folder 180)
- #2493b (Box 71, Folder 181)
- #2501 (Box 71, Folder 182)
- #2513a (Box 71, Folder 183)
- #2513b (Box 71, Folder 184)
- #2513c (Box 71, Folder 185)
- #2514 (Box 71, Folder 186)
- #2521 (Box 71, Folder 187)
- #2528 (Box 71, Folder 188)
- #2563 (Box 71, Folder 189)
- #2566 (Box 71, Folder 190)
- #2599 (Box 71, Folder 191)
- #2604 (Box 71, Folder 192)
- #2607 (Box 71, Folder 193)
- #2608 (Box 71, Folder 194)
- #2630 (Box 71, Folder 195)
- #2646 (Box 71, Folder 196)
- #2647 (Box 71, Folder 197)
- #2651 (Box 71, Folder 198)
- #2665 (Box 71, Folder 199)
- #2686 (Box 71, Folder 200)
- #2693 (Box 71, Folder 201)
- #2728 (Box 71, Folder 202)
- #2733 (Box 71, Folder 203)
- #2735 (Box 71, Folder 204)
- #2746 (Box 71, Folder 205)
- #2750 (Box 71, Folder 206)
- #2757 (Box 71, Folder 207)
- #2764 (Box 71, Folder 208)
- #2775a (Box 71, Folder 209)
- #2775b (Box 71, Folder 210)
- #2790 (Box 71, Folder 211)
- #2794 (Box 71, Folder 212)
- #2800 (Box 71, Folder 213)
- #2846 (Box 71, Folder 214)
- Index of images (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Index of images (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Index of images (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Index of images (Box 75, Folder 1)
- 1P (Box 76, Folder 1)
- 1N (Box 76, Folder 2)
- 2P (Box 76, Folder 3)
- 2N (Box 76, Folder 4)
- 3P (Box 76, Folder 5)
- 4N (Box 76, Folder 6)
- 4P (Box 76, Folder 7)
- 5P (Box 76, Folder 8)
- 5N (Box 76, Folder 9)
- 6P (Box 76, Folder 10)
- 6N (Box 76, Folder 11)
- 7N (Box 76, Folder 12)
- 8N (Box 76, Folder 13)
- 9P (Box 76, Folder 14)
- 9P (Box 76, Folder 14)
- 9N (Box 76, Folder 15)
- 10P (Box 76, Folder 16)
- 10N (Box 76, Folder 17)
- 11P (Box 76, Folder 18)
- 11N (Box 76, Folder 19)
- 12P (Box 76, Folder 20)
- 12N (Box 76, Folder 21)
- 13P (Box 76, Folder 22)
- 13N (Box 76, Folder 23)
- 14P (Box 76, Folder 24)
- 14N (Box 76, Folder 25)
- 15N (Box 76, Folder 26)
- 16P (Box 76, Folder 27)
- 16N (Box 76, Folder 28)
- 17P (Box 76, Folder 29)
- 17N (Box 76, Folder 30)
- 18N (Box 76, Folder 31)
- 19N (Box 76, Folder 32)
- 1P (Box 76, Folder 33)
- 1N (Box 76, Folder 34)
- 2N (Box 76, Folder 35)
- 3P (Box 76, Folder 36)
- 3N (Box 76, Folder 37)
- 4P (Box 76, Folder 38)
- 4N (Box 76, Folder 39)
- 5P (Box 76, Folder 40)
- 5N (Box 76, Folder 41)
- 6P (Box 76, Folder 42)
- 6N (Box 76, Folder 43)
- 7P (Box 76, Folder 44)
- 7N (Box 76, Folder 45)
- 8N (Box 76, Folder 46)
- 9N (Box 76, Folder 47)
- 10P (Box 76, Folder 48)
- 10N (Box 76, Folder 49)
- 11P (Box 76, Folder 50)
- 11N (Box 76, Folder 51)
- 12P (Box 76, Folder 52)
- 12N (Box 76, Folder 53)
- 13N (Box 76, Folder 54)
- 14P (Box 76, Folder 55)
- 14N (Box 76, Folder 56)
- 15N (Box 76, Folder 57)
- 16P (Box 76, Folder 58)
- 16N (Box 76, Folder 59)
- 17P (Box 76, Folder 60)
- 17N (Box 76, Folder 61)
- 18N (Box 76, Folder 62)
- 19P (Box 76, Folder 63)
- 19N (Box 76, Folder 64)
- 20P (Box 76, Folder 65)
- 20N (Box 76, Folder 66)
- 21P (Box 76, Folder 67)
- 21N (Box 76, Folder 68)
- 22P (Box 76, Folder 69)
- 21N (Box 76, Folder 70)
- 22P (Box 76, Folder 71)
- 23P (Box 76, Folder 72)
- 23N (Box 76, Folder 73)
- 24N (Box 76, Folder 74)
- 25P (Box 76, Folder 75)
- 25N (Box 76, Folder 76)
- 26P (Box 76, Folder 77)
- 26N (Box 76, Folder 78)
- 27P (Box 76, Folder 79)
- 27N (Box 76, Folder 80)
- 28P (Box 76, Folder 81)
- 28N (Box 76, Folder 82)
- 29N (Box 76, Folder 83)
- 30P (Box 76, Folder 84)
- 30N (Box 76, Folder 85)
- 31N (Box 76, Folder 86)
- 20P (Box 76, Folder 87)
- 20N (Box 76, Folder 88)
- 21P (Box 76, Folder 89)
- 21N (Box 76, Folder 90)
- 22P (Box 76, Folder 91)
- 22N (Box 76, Folder 92)
- 23P (Box 76, Folder 93)
- 23N (Box 76, Folder 94)
- 24N (Box 76, Folder 95)
- 25P (Box 76, Folder 96)
- 25N (Box 76, Folder 97)
- NO # (Box 76, Folder 98)
- 26N (Box 76, Folder 99)
- 27N (Box 76, Folder 100)
- 28P (Box 76, Folder 101)
- 28N (Box 76, Folder 102)
- 29N (Box 76, Folder 103)
- 30N (Box 76, Folder 104)
- 31P (Box 76, Folder 105)
- 31N (Box 76, Folder 106)
- 32P (Box 76, Folder 107)
- 32N (Box 76, Folder 108)
- 33N (Box 76, Folder 109)
- 34N (Box 76, Folder 110)
- 35P (Box 76, Folder 111)
- 35N (Box 76, Folder 112)
- 36P (Box 76, Folder 113)
- 36N (Box 76, Folder 114)
- 37P (Box 76, Folder 115)
- 37N (Box 76, Folder 116)
- 38P (Box 76, Folder 117)
- 38N (Box 76, Folder 118)
- 39P (Box 76, Folder 119)
- 39N (Box 76, Folder 120)
- 40P (Box 76, Folder 121)
- 40N (Box 76, Folder 122)
- 41P (Box 76, Folder 123)
- 41N (Box 76, Folder 124)
- 42P (Box 76, Folder 125)
- 42N (Box 76, Folder 126)
- 43P (Box 76, Folder 127)
- 43N (Box 76, Folder 128)
- NO# (Box 76, Folder 129)